Samantha Dickeson

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Graduate of Founders and Coders, loving JavaScript web development. I like making things, solving problems and making things that solve problems.

I'm a Psychology graduate, and before learning web development I worked in data analysis for four years, teaching myself SQL, VBA and a smattering of Python.

FOUNDERS AND CODERS

Founders and Coders, Finsbury Park

MARCH 2019 - JULY 2019

Founders and Coders are a non-profit based in Finsbury Park, London. They run peer-led full-stack web development courses which are free but highly selective.

There is a heavy focus on cooperation and all our coding is done by pair programming.

After learning web development, we gain hands on design and build sprint experience using Agile methodology working on exciting <u>tech for better</u> projects.

EXPERIENCE

Vanguard Learning Trust, Ickenham — *Data Manager*

DECEMBER 2015 - MARCH 2019

My responsibilities included analysing student performance data for target setting and reporting to senior leadership. I gained a lot of experience in MS Excel and Google Sheets, teaching myself VBA and Google Apps Script to create dynamic reports and data visualisations.

Xerox UK, Uxbridge — Data Migration Analyst

MARCH 2015 - DECEMBER 2015

I managed qualification related data on the company data system SAP. As I picked up VBA and SQL, I began to produce mini 'applications' for employees and managers to access and transfer data.

My github is:

■ github.com/starsuit

See my favourite projects:

starsuit.netlify.com

Email me:

■ samlucydickeson@gmail.com

Find me on linkedin:

■ linkedin.com/in/samantha-dickeson

STACK / SKILLS

- HTML and CSS
- Accessibility and design
- Git and GitHub
- Vanilla JavaScript
- Test-driven development
- Pair programming
- Node and npm
- Express
- Handlebars
- PostgreSQL
- Heroku deployment
- React
- Python and Django

EDUCATION

Reading University — BSc Psychology 2:1

OCTOBER 2010 - JUNE 2014

Vyners School, Ickenham SEPTEMBER 2003 - JULY 2010



@starsuit



@star_suit



@Starsuit